https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/0s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/5s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/10s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/15s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/20s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/25s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/30s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/35s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/40s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/45s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/50s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/55s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/1m0s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/1m5s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/1m10s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/1m15s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/1m20s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/1m25s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/1m30s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/1m35s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/1m40s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/1m45s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/1m50s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/1m55s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/2m0s/match/image.jpeg
https://videos.skynews.com/image/v1/jit/6058004172001/98a7af29-fd16-4ff7-bec8-d22ea74cd79a/main/180x320/2m5s/match/image.jpeg